# Edwin León Herrera

Heredia, Costa Rica · Edwin León | LinkedIn · +506 8975 3995 · edwin1224leon@gmail.com

I'm a passionate Software Developer, with more than 3 years of experience, I consider this area the most important since nowadays we live in a digital world. To stay updated in this amazing world, I like to take courses, watch video tutorials, read documentation, and do many proofs of concepts to test new features.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Tiims Revolution Heredia, Costa Rica

FullStack Developer

Dec 2021 - To date

- Develop sections of web pages between ASP.NET and React.
- Development of a dashboard section with graphs and tables for a stock market investment company with React and ASP.NET.
- Creating a to-do list page and mobile app using React, React Native, and GraphQL.
- Development of a simple page using React and Strapi.
- Development and improvement of a tour page using React, GraphQL, and Contentful.
- Developing and improving a smart locker platform, creating and exporting dashboards, charts, online payments, and code optimization.
- Creating restful APIs with Node.js
- Creating GraphQL APIs.
- Development, improvement, and maintenance of a blog-type page.

## Fujitsu GDC Costa Rica

Heredia, Costa Rica Aug 2021 – May 2022

Help Desk Agent

- Support users with Office and Windows problems.
- Technical support to users on problems with Salesforce, company VPN, and other company platforms.

#### **Datasys Group S.A**

Heredia, Costa Rica

NOC Agent

Oct 2018 – Sep 2021

- Real-time monitoring of critical network infrastructure to keep customer services always up and running
- Maintenance and update of network devices (Routers, Firewall, etc.)
- Manage customer network traffic (website permissions, network permissions, user permissions, etc.)

# **EDUCATION**

#### Universidad Americana

Heredia, Costa Rica

Bachelor's degree in Systems Engineering

Sep 2018 - Dec 2024

#### **ADITIONAL SKILLS**

- Native Spanish speaker.
- B2 level in English.